And so I, a Salem vs Ellusia, shall take count slain Sosbom Troyard for my husband, and I also proclaim that a new kingdom is now established for us in Earthspace.
My daring and resourceful knights, despite our best efforts, indications are that this war may become more protracted than was foreseen. What should our course of action be, now that we are at this turning point?
Is this the time for orbital knights to squabble amongst themselves over petty power and credit?
No, we must now join together, all under one flag, and fight for the future of verse.
As evidence of my earnestness in this regard, I now delegate all of my authority to the lord of this newly reactivated castle, my soon-to-be spouse, Count Troyard.
This includes the right to decide upon whom to bestow the power to awaken old Noah.
Until the day we achieve victory in this war, I have the utmost faith and hope you will listen to Count Troyard, know that his words are mine, and rally to his side.
And we shall do it all for verse.
Tanya then?
Tanya-
Thank you.
Yes, sir.
But, my lord, for those knights who are anxious regarding this situation,
Her Highness' words must have fallen on their ears like a divine revelation.
Revelation?
You are her power now.
Her decrees and proclamations were only because of you.
And everyone knows this.
Tonight's unhappy about the current state.
They were words from on high.
Surely they must feel their prayers for a true leader have finally been answered.
You exaggerate.
Because the fact is, rebel factions will certainly begin to show up as well.
And that's an area where I think you'll be useful.
Do you wish a display of power?
Is that it, my lord count?
No.
Engaging with these people will become an endless exercise.
So, first we boot them out.
Then we let the proper authorities take it from there.
My lord?
Princess Asalem's name will be all that's needed.
Then, it should be simple enough to strip them of their knighthoods with a random accusation.
Do I sense disapproval of this action?
No, my lord.
In fact, quite the opposite.
A true leader stops at nothing to achieve his goals.
Ever since the announcement, my lord, if I may be so bold, you seem to be preparing for the very worst.
I always wanted to be close to her highness.
My only wish was to be worthy of her.
Somehow, someday, to be of service to her.
But I...
If power is all I can win, then that must become my goal.
Is that you, Harklight?
Enter.
A lord slain.
Yes, Adel Ritzo?
We are satisfied with your ship's deployment and your existing personnel.
For the time being, we want your continued support as a current ad hoc commando squad.
No objection to those orders, sir.
However, as to Princess Asalem's recent speech...
That nonsense about founding a new dynasty in Earth space?
That is nothing but big talk meant to stir up the Mars Knights.
A morale booster.
Yes, that might be the case.
But then, we also might want to consider that we're looking at a possible escalation of the enemy's war efforts.
Do you think we're just sitting on our hands, doing nothing?
Is that what you're implying here?
No, sir.
I did not mean that at all.
As far as any new operations, we are in the process of assigning our primary units.
Once our strategic planning is finalized, you will be contacted.
Captain, you might not care for your status as a commando unit, but there's a limit to how much faith we can put in a ship running on enemy power.
That's just the way it is.
I'm amazed you got through that without some outburst.
What?
Do you think that's what I should have done?
Remember, I'm only here serving as your escort on this.
And anyway, I'm not nearly as naive as I look.
They don't get it.
They don't understand.
I don't think they have a clue what they've got here.
And we're doing the best we can.
No.
I'm not talking about how they're treating us, or the Ducalian.
They're not taking this seriously.
What do you mean?
They don't know the Martians.
Right now, the war is going in our favor a tiny bit, and they're acting like it's all one and done.
That's terrifying.
I will drain the therapeutic fluid and take Her Royal Highness back to my castle.
Tell no one of this.
Not even Princess Lamarina.
Why not tell me?
Do as I say!
I apologize.
I did not mean to startle you.
No visitors allowed?
Her condition is that serious?
Is it a turn for the worse?
Perhaps it is.
It's a miracle that she has held on as long as she has.
Could we lose her today?
Tomorrow?
They say they just don't know.
It is possible she could remain in this condition indefinitely.
Hmm.
I see.
I can only guess how you feel.
You may well have mixed emotions.
However, she is your only sibling by blood.
You are the one feeling sadness.
Isn't that right?
You, Slane.
I must go now.
Slane!
I forgive you for that.
Even if you broke down and wept in front of me.
Shedding tears for her loss.
Because I am...
I am already yours.
Could I have triggered it?
I didn't...
Really mean...
I always did admire you.
You had everything that I did not.
So I hated you too.
Still, no need to worry, sister.
From now on, I will truly be your substitute.
And as for Slane, I will give him the support he needs.
Why am I crying?
Hmm.
Come on now.
What's up with that?
Are you saying the captain just ditched her here?
The captain left me in charge because she thinks I can handle the job.
At least that's what she said.
But Commander Mitsuzaki has obviously got to be just devastated.
Of all people, why pick Lieutenant Marito for a traveling companion?
Companion?
Nah, he's more like an escort.
What's this about, Lieutenant Marito?
Uh, nothing at all, really.
It's just that he went along with the captain to that briefing,
so I thought it might be something serious.
I see.
Well, with that proclamation by the princess,
the situation is definitely changing minute to minute.
I just find it hard to believe she's gonna marry that count.
You care about that?
No, but think about it.
Isn't it possible that this big change of heart
was because someone close to her felt that way?
You know, some deal where she got seduced into it and...
Sorry.
But we're still not 100% sure, are we?
That the princess of Salem in the speech we just heard
is the same one who is with us?
She didn't talk like that when she was down here.
To tell you the truth, I have no idea.
Inaho insists she's actually an imposter, but how can we tell?
Well, there's no way to know just how much he really can see.
Have you eaten anything?
In a little while.
Let me find a good place to leave off.
You've been this way since we were just kids.
When you're into something, the world fades away.
Here.
That's great.
Thanks, Yuki.
You've heard, right?
About the speech of Salem made?
Yes.
I have to admit, that proclamation seemed to prove everything you've been saying.
And it all seems a little too convenient.
If that really was the real princess of Salem,
she would never think of founding a new kingdom and killing to do it.
Slain Troyard.
You mean that douchebag who shot my little brother in the head?
Thank you for caring.
You might want to watch your language, Yuki.
Honestly, it just doesn't matter anymore whether she's real or not.
I don't think anyone would listen to her now.
Even if she was trying to promote genuine peace between Earth and Mars again.
About the attack on Earth, my lord.
If there are no problems, I will get preparations underway.
Is all well, my lord?
I'm listening.
We will proceed as planned.
Yes, sir.
And, her highness?
She will wake soon.
I know it.
I, too, eagerly await that day.
Truly, my lord.
But, should we also fear it?
Sir?
Never mind.
Has there been any change at all?
No, my lord.
They believe she could remain like this for some time.
So then we will wait.
I am accustomed to that, right?
I think that she will be very surprised.
When she wakes up again, she'll see how much everything has changed.
And will I?
Will I seem different to her as well?
She will think, what a fine man it is you've grown into.
I am sure.
I shall return.
My lord slain!
Tell her it's so.
Oh, my lady.
Is it you?
My lady's awake.
She came back.
Your highness, it is me, slain.
I'm right here.
Do you see?
I'm slain.
Slain Troyard.
Troyard.
Your highness.
I've waited so very long to hear you say my name, to hear you speak again.
Do you see me?
Don't lie.
Let me see.
I haven't happened to you.
I haven't been hurt.
To be continued...
I deeply regret causing you worry, Count Baracruz.
And what are your plans now?
I have none as of yet, and I have also lost my cataphract.
If you wish to ally with Count Troyart, I could intercede on your behalf.
About Count Marilsian, I heard of the event. It must be a continuing wound for you.
No. Both sides fought fairly, and that was just the way things came out. I have no cause to hold a grudge.
Please, my lord, Count. Troyart is dangerous. Not only did he kill Marilsian, there are even suspicions that he was responsible for the death of Count Sarsgård.
Who would say that? Be cautious.
I merely thought you...
Hold your tongue, my lord. Obviously, you are the victim of unfounded rumors.
I take it you were privileged to hear Princess of Salem's proclamation.
There is no one who can stop Count Troyart's illustrious rise.
Not with his power including all Noah activation privileges.
It would be like fighting a sandstorm on Olympus.
If you wish to remain among the orbital knights, I suggest you act wisely.
Count Barocruz has pledged full and unconditional cooperation.
Count Zebron and Raffia have yet to make it clear what their allegiances will be.
But they appear amenable to acknowledging the new kingdom.
Morale has risen throughout the base.
And we have almost finished going through the list of knights who seem likely to oppose you.
We are ready to take forceful steps at a moment's notice.
My lord Slane?
You seem quite troubled.
Pardon, my lord.
Is it to do with Princess of Salem's recovery?
You want me to give Adel Ritzo some time off?
Yes. Perhaps only for a short time.
It's obvious she's out of sorts.
The change in Asalem's status was a shock.
I can see that it would be.
Tell me, how are you bearing up under all this slain?
I do worry for you.
I thank you for your concern.
You see, you are the only one that I know I can count on completely.
I will take verse and make it mine, for her highness.
Ma'am, both Dales and Orlov platoons are currently on the march towards the enemy landing castle.
Attention, Clydesdale and Mustang platoons.
Stay on high alert for the enemy cataphract.
As soon as you identify it, attack immediately and take it out.
How lovely.
Yes.
My lord's lane had this garden made just for you, m'lady.
Is that right?
It looks just as it did on Earth.
It does.
Are your memories coming back from when you were there?
Birds.
I was watching them, with that boy.
Inaho Kaisuka?
You mean him?
Kaisuka.
Is there something wrong?
Uh, no.
Look, m'lady, right over there.
Isn't that pretty?
This is Dales' platoon leader.
We are closing on the enemy landing castle with Orlov platoon.
Clydesdale platoon.
Those arrows have powerful explosive charges on them, so careful, everyone!
Bastard!
Easy, don't waste your ammunition.
The enemy is cloaked and moving real fast out there.
We know they're using arrows, which is probably two.
Right.
Muzzle flashes would make it a simple matter to pinpoint their location.
The arrows must be to avoid that.
Optical shielding.
An invisibility cloak.
Yeah, something like that.
Anyway, it's very ingenious.
There's nothing showing on my thermograph.
It doesn't cast a shadow.
But it does.
You can trust me when I say that it's there.
Right.
For me, m'lord?
Customize it to suit your taste.
I've already discussed your rank in Alt-Noah activation with Princess Lemrina.
Thank you, my lord.
The arrow is gone from the bow.
Now there is no turning back.
Yes, sir.
Now notify the counts at once.
Zebron, Raffia, and Olga.
Tell them to swear their allegiance.
Smoke grenades now locked and loaded.
And I'm ready here.
Fire!
He's right.
It definitely exists.
And as long as it's there,
it's going to have an effect on air currents.
Target located.
Right.
Stand by to fire.
Lieutenant!
What is it, Kaiska?
On our three o'clock.
New enemy!
Closing in from dead ahead.
They're coming at us in a team attack?
Overhead two!
Incoming!
A landing castle.
All units, brace for impact!
Multiple landing castings.
Multiple vessels.
Multiple cataphracts.
Simultaneous coordination.
He's made his move.
It's him.
So, no time for doubts anymore.
There is no returning from where I am now.
Billy.
elly's son dugup.
Hmm.
You're so old.
It says they look the beautiful relação among you.
Take it.
Bokutats và
Thank you.
Hasta la fin.
Let's believe the beginning of the beginning
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh